<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="accept_and_continue">[Åççéþţ &amp; çöñţîñûé one two three]</string>
    <string name="access_list_of_links">[Åççéšš å ļîšţ öƒ ļîñķš one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_block_warning_do">"[Çéŕţåîñ åççéššîбîļîţý šéŕvîçéš åŕéñ'ţ åļļöŵéð. Îƒ ţĥéý åŕéñ'ţ ðéåçţîvåţéð, ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_block_warning_po">"[Çéŕţåîñ åççéššîбîļîţý šéŕvîçéš åŕéñ'ţ åļļöŵéð. Îƒ ţĥéý åŕéñ'ţ ðéåçţîvåţéð, ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_incompliant_button">[Ĝö ţö åççéššîбîļîţý šéţţîñĝš one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_incompliant_title">[Ðéåçţîvåţé åççéššîбîļîţý šéŕvîçéš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_wipe_warning_do">"[Çéŕţåîñ åççéššîбîļîţý šéŕvîçéš åŕéñ'ţ åļļöŵéð. Îƒ ţĥéý åŕéñ'ţ ðéåçţîvåţéð, ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="accessibility_service_wipe_warning_po">"[Çéŕţåîñ åççéššîбîļîţý šéŕvîçéš åŕéñ'ţ åļļöŵéð. Îƒ ţĥéý åŕéñ'ţ ðéåçţîvåţéð, ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ бé ŕémövéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]"</string>
    <string name="account_management_disclaimer_header">[Ýöûŕ åççöûñţ îš måñåĝéð one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="account_management_disclaimer_subheader">[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ûšéš möбîļé måñåĝéméñţ ţö éñƒöŕçé šéçûŕîţý þöļîçîéš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="action_tap_to_configure_accessibility_services">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ðöéšñ'ţ åļļöŵ åţ ļéåšţ öñé öƒ ýöûŕ ðévîçé'š åççéššîбîļîţý šéŕvîçéš. Öñçé ţĥé šéŕvîçé îš ðîšåбļéð, îţ çåñ'ţ бé ûšéð åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone]"</string>
    <string name="action_tap_to_configure_input_methods">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ðöéšñ'ţ åļļöŵ åţ ļéåšţ öñé öƒ ýöûŕ ðévîçé'š ķéýбöåŕðš. Öñçé ţĥé ķéýбöåŕð îš ðîšåбļéð, îţ çåñ'ţ бé ûšéð åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen]"</string>
    <string name="action_tap_to_go_to_app_usage_permission_settings">[Ţĥé Åñðŕöîð Ðévîçé Þöļîçý åþþ ñééðš þéŕmîššîöñ ţö åççéšš ýöûŕ ðévîçé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="action_tap_to_set_password">[Çĥööšé å ÞÎÑ, þåţţéŕñ, öŕ þåššŵöŕð one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="action_tap_to_set_password_device">[Çĥööšé å ÞÎÑ, þåţţéŕñ, öŕ þåššŵöŕð ƒöŕ ţĥîš ðévîçé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="action_tap_to_set_password_profile">[Çĥööšé å ÞÎÑ, þåţţéŕñ, öŕ þåššŵöŕð ƒöŕ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="action_touch_to_view_details">[Ţåþ ţö vîéŵ ðéţåîļš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="activating_reset_password_token_error">[Éŕŕöŕ åçţîvåţîñĝ ŕéšéţ þåššŵöŕð ţöķéñ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="add_account_action_button">[Åðð åççöûñţ one two]</string>
    <string name="add_account_failure">[Fåîļéð ţö åðð åççöûñţ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="add_personal_account_description">[Ñöŵ ţĥåţ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé îš ŕéåðý, ýöû çåñ åðð å þéŕšöñåļ Ĝööĝļé Åççöûñţ ţö åççéšš ýöûŕ åþþš åñð çöñţéñţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
    <string name="add_personal_account_description_device_owner">[Ţö šéþåŕåţé ŵöŕķ ðåţå ƒŕöm þéŕšöñåļ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="add_personal_account_title">[Åðð å þéŕšöñåļ åççöûñţ ţö ĝéţ möŕé ƒŕöm ýöûŕ ðévîçé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="add_personal_account_title_device_owner">[Åðð ýöûŕ þéŕšöñåļ åççöûñţ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="add_personal_account_title_v2">[Åðð å þéŕšöñåļ åççöûñţ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="add_wifi_manually">[Åðð Ñéţŵöŕķ one two]</string>
    <string name="admin_has_ability_to_monitor_device">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ĥåš ţĥé åбîļîţý ţö möñîţöŕ åñð måñåĝé šéţţîñĝš, çöŕþöŕåţé åççéšš, åþþš, þéŕmîššîöñš, åñð ðåţå åššöçîåţéð ŵîţĥ ţĥîš ᐅ%1$sᐊ, îñçļûðîñĝ ýöûŕ ñéţŵöŕķ åçţîvîţý, åš ŵéļļ åš ýöûŕ ðévîçé'š ļöçåţîöñ, çåļļ ĥîšţöŕý, åñð çöñţåçţ šéåŕçĥ ĥîšţöŕý.ᐅ

ᐊÇöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ möŕé îñƒöŕmåţîöñ, îñçļûðîñĝ ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ'š þŕîvåçý þöļîçîéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo thirtythree thirtyfour thirtyfive thirtysix thirtyseven thirtyeight thirtynine]"</string>
    <string name="admin_has_ability_to_monitor_profile">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ĥåš ţĥé åбîļîţý ţö möñîţöŕ åñð måñåĝé šéţţîñĝš, çöŕþöŕåţé åççéšš, åþþš, þéŕmîššîöñš, åñð ðåţå åššöçîåţéð ŵîţĥ ţĥîš þŕöƒîļé, îñçļûðîñĝ ýöûŕ ñéţŵöŕķ åçţîvîţý, åš ŵéļļ åš ýöûŕ ðévîçé'š ļöçåţîöñ, çåļļ ĥîšţöŕý, åñð çöñţåçţ šéåŕçĥ ĥîšţöŕý.ᐅ

ᐊÇöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ möŕé îñƒöŕmåţîöñ, îñçļûðîñĝ ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ'š þŕîvåçý þöļîçîéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo thirtythree thirtyfour thirtyfive thirtysix thirtyseven thirtyeight thirtynine forty]"</string>
    <string name="already_enabled_debug_items">[Åļŕéåðý éñåбļéð ðéбûĝ îţémš one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="app_crash_desc">[Ţŕý ŕéšţåŕţîñĝ ýöûŕ ðévîçé, öŕ çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="app_crash_title">"[Åþþ îšñ'ţ ŵöŕķîñĝ one two three]"</string>
    <string name="app_install_failed_desc">[Fåîļéð ţö îñšţåļļ ᐅ%1$sᐊ. ᐅ%2$sᐊ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="app_install_failed_single_app_desc">"[Šéţ-ûþ çåñ'ţ бé çömþļéţéð åš ᐅ%1$sᐊ îš å ŕéqûîŕéð åþþ. Þļéåšé çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ šýšţém åðmîñîšţŕåţöŕ ðîŕéçţļý. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="app_install_failure_no_license_remaining">[Ñö möŕé ļîçéñšé ƒöŕ åþþ éxîšţš. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="app_install_failure_not_compatible">[Åþþ îš ñöţ çömþåţîбļé ŵîţĥ ţĥîš ðévîçé. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="app_install_failure_not_enrolled">[Ðévîçé îš ñöţ éñŕöļļéð. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="app_install_failure_not_found">[Åþþ ŵåš ñöţ ƒöûñð. one two three four]</string>
    <string name="app_install_failure_permissions_not_accepted">[Þéñðîñĝ åçţîöñ ƒŕöm ýöûŕ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="app_install_failure_timeout">[Ţîméð öûţ ŵåîţîñĝ ƒöŕ åþþ ţö îñšţåļļ. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="app_install_failure_transient_error">[Ţŕåñšîéñţ éŕŕöŕ îñšţåļļîñĝ åþþ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="app_install_failure_unavailable_country">[Åþþ îš ûñåvåîļåбļé îñ ýöûŕ çöûñţŕý. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="app_install_failure_unknown">"[Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ'š åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="app_installed_block_warning_do">"[Îƒ ᐅ%1$sᐊ îšñ'ţ ûñîñšţåļļéð, ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="app_installed_block_warning_po">"[Îƒ ᐅ%1$sᐊ îšñ'ţ ûñîñšţåļļéð, ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="app_installed_incompliant_title">[Ûñîñšţåļļ ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three]</string>
    <string name="app_installed_wipe_warning_do">"[Îƒ ᐅ%1$sᐊ îšñ'ţ ûñîñšţåļļéð, ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="app_installed_wipe_warning_po">"[Îƒ ᐅ%1$sᐊ îšñ'ţ ûñîñšţåļļéð, ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ бé ŕémövéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="app_label">[Ŵöŕķ Šéţûþ one two]</string>
    <string name="app_not_updated_block_warning_do">"[Îƒ ᐅ%1$sᐊ îšñ'ţ ûþðåţéð, ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]"</string>
    <string name="app_not_updated_block_warning_po">"[Îƒ ᐅ%1$sᐊ îšñ'ţ ûþðåţéð, ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="app_not_updated_button">[Öþéñ Þļåý Šţöŕé one two]</string>
    <string name="app_not_updated_incompliant_title">[Ûþðåţé ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three]</string>
    <string name="app_not_updated_wipe_warning_do">"[Îƒ ᐅ%1$sᐊ îšñ'ţ ûþðåţéð, ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]"</string>
    <string name="app_not_updated_wipe_warning_po">"[Îƒ ᐅ%1$sᐊ îšñ'ţ ûþðåţéð, ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ бé ŕémövéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="apps_tutorial_details">[Бŕöŵšé ţĥé måñåĝéð Ĝööĝļé Þļåý Šţöŕé ƒöŕ åþþŕövéð ŵöŕķ åþþš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="apps_tutorial_title">[Fîñð åþþš ƒöŕ ŵöŕķ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="await_apps_install_additional_apps">[Åððîţîöñåļ åþþš (ᐅ%1$dᐊ) one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="await_apps_install_completed_description">[Ŕéqûîŕéð åþþš îñšţåļļéð. Þŕéšš ñéxţ бûţţöñ ţö çöñţîñûé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="await_apps_install_icon_done_description">[Åþþ îñšţåļļéð one two]</string>
    <string name="await_apps_install_icon_error_description">[Åþþ îñšţåļļ ƒåîļéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="await_apps_install_icon_waiting_description">[Ŵåîţîñĝ ţö îñšţåļļ åþþ… one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="await_apps_install_list_item_description_installed">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ, îñšţåļļéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="await_apps_install_list_item_description_installing">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ, îñšţåļļîñĝ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="await_apps_install_required_apps">[Ŕéqûîŕéð åþþš (ᐅ%1$dᐊ) one two three four]</string>
    <string name="await_apps_install_screen_title">[Îñšţåļļ ŵöŕķ åþþš one two three]</string>
    <string name="await_apps_install_skip_button_description">[Ţåķîñĝ ţöö ļöñĝ¿ Åþþš ŵîļļ çöñţîñûé îñšţåļļîñĝ îñ ţĥé бåçķĝŕöûñð åƒţéŕ ýöû šķîþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="badged_apps_details">[Éåçĥ ŵöŕķ åþþ ĥåš å бåðĝé åñð çåñ бé mövéð ţö ýöûŕ Ĥömé šçŕééñ ƒöŕ éåšîéŕ åççéšš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="badged_apps_title">[Åççéšš ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="beam_title">[Îñšţåļļ ŵöŕķ åþþš one two three]</string>
    <string name="brand_screen_header">[Ţĥîš ðévîçé бéļöñĝš ţö ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="button_feedback">[Ĥéļþ &amp; ƒééðбåçķ one two]</string>
    <string name="camera_failed_message">[Çåññöţ çöññéçţ ţö çåméŕå, šŵîţçĥîñĝ ţö ţéxţ îñþûţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="camera_failed_title">[Çåméŕå éŕŕöŕ one two]</string>
    <string name="cancel">[Çåñçéļ one]</string>
    <string name="cancel_provisioning">[Çåñçéļ one]</string>
    <string name="cancel_setup">[Çåñçéļ šéţûþ one two]</string>
    <string name="cancel_setup_dialog_text">[Çåñçéļ šéţûþ¿ one two]</string>
    <string name="cannot_be_setup_with_current_account_message">"[Ţĥîš ðévîçé çåñ'ţ бé šéţ ûþ ûšîñĝ ţĥé åççöûñţ ýöû šîĝñéð îñ ŵîţĥ. Þļéåšé ƒåçţöŕý ŕéšéţ ţĥé ðévîçé åñð ţŕý ûšîñĝ å ðîƒƒéŕéñţ ŵöŕķ åççöûñţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone]"</string>
    <string name="cant_add_work_profile">"[Çåñ'ţ åðð ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="cant_set_up_device">"[Çåñ'ţ šéţ ûþ ðévîçé one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="cant_set_up_profile">"[Çåñ'ţ šéţ ûþ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="change_device_launcher">[Çĥåñĝé ðévîçé ļåûñçĥéŕ one two three]</string>
    <string name="check_enrollment_token_title">[Çĥéçķîñĝ çöðéû2026 one two three]</string>
    <string name="choose_network_description">"[Çöññéçţ ţö Ŵî-Fî ţö ûþðåţé ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ'š þöļîçîéš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="choose_network_title">[Çĥööšé å ţémþöŕåŕý ñéţŵöŕķ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="choose_wifi_connection">[Çĥööšé ŴîFî Ñéţŵöŕķ one two three]</string>
    <string name="close">[Çļöšé one]</string>
    <string name="close_list">[Çļöšé ļîšţ one two]</string>
    <string name="confirm_credentials_description">[Þļéåšé çöñƒîŕm çŕéðéñţîåļš ţö åçţîvåţé ŕémöţé þåššŵöŕð ŕéšéţ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="confirm_credentials_title">[Þļéåšé çöñƒîŕm çŕéðéñţîåļš one two three]</string>
    <string name="contact_admin_desc">[Îƒ ýöû ĥåvé åñý qûéšţîöñš, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="contact_device_provider">[Ţö ļéåŕñ möŕé, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ᐅ%1$sᐊ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="contact_your_admin_for_help">[Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="content_description_launch_screen_icon">[Ļåûñçĥ šçŕééñ îçöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="continue_provisioning_notify_text">[Ţåþ ţö çöñţîñûé šéţţîñĝ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="continue_provisioning_notify_title">[Éñçŕýþţîöñ çömþļéţé one two three]</string>
    <string name="cope_provisioning_step_1_header">[Ŵöŕķ åþþš åŕé ķéþţ îñ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé &amp; måñåĝéð бý ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="cope_provisioning_step_2_header">[Þéŕšöñåļ åþþš åŕé šéþåŕåţé &amp; ĥîððéñ ƒŕöm ŵöŕķ åþþš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="cope_provisioning_step_3_header">[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ çåñ çöñţŕöļ ţĥîš ᐅ%1$sᐊ &amp; бļöçķ çéŕţåîñ åþþš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="cope_provisioning_summary">[Ŵöŕķ åþþš åŕé ķéþţ îñ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé åñð måñåĝéð бý ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. Þéŕšöñåļ åþþš åŕé šéþåŕåţé åñð ĥîððéñ ƒŕöm ŵöŕķ åþþš. Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ çåñ çöñţŕöļ ţĥîš ᐅ%1$sᐊ åñð бļöçķ çéŕţåîñ åþþš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive]</string>
    <string name="could_not_create_new_enrollment_token">[Éñŕöļļméñţ ţöķéñ çöûļð ñöţ бé çŕéåţéð. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="current_item_status">%3$s. Step %1$d of %2$d.</string>
    <string name="default_lost_mode_message">If found, please contact the details below</string>
    <string name="default_managed_profile_name">[Ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two]</string>
    <string name="default_owned_device_username">[Ûšéŕ öƒ ŵöŕķ ðévîçé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="default_sync_time">[Ñöţ šýñçéð one two]</string>
    <string name="device_admin_installing_tutorial_details">[Ýöû çåñ ķééþ ûšîñĝ ýöûŕ ðévîçé ðûŕîñĝ šéţûþ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="device_admin_installing_tutorial_title">[Šéţţîñĝ ûþ ýöûŕ ðévîçéû2026 one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="device_admin_managed">[Ţĥîš ðévîçé îš åðmîñîšţéŕéð бý ᐅ%sᐊ. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="device_already_set_up">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ îš åļŕéåðý šéţ ûþ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="device_blocked">[Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="device_blocked_details">[Ţö šéţ ûþ ţĥîš ðévîçé, åšķ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ţö åççéþţ ţĥé Ţéŕmš öƒ Šéŕvîçé ƒöŕ Åñðŕöîð Éñţéŕþŕîšé Éššéñţîåļš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
    <string name="device_details_activity_title">[Ðévîçé îñƒö ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ çåñ šéé one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="device_has_reset_protection_contact_admin">[Ýöûŕ ᐅ%1$sᐊ ĥåš ŕéšéţ þŕöţéçţîöñ ţûŕñéð öñ. Föŕ ĥéļþ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="device_incompliant_device_disabled_title">"[Ţĥîš ðévîçé îšñ'ţ åçţîvé one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="device_incompliant_title">[Åçţîöñ ŕéqûîŕéð one two]</string>
    <string name="device_information_android_build_number">[Åñðŕöîð бûîļð ñûmбéŕ one two three]</string>
    <string name="device_information_android_build_time">[Åñðŕöîð бûîļð ţîmé one two three]</string>
    <string name="device_information_android_build_type">[Åñðŕöîð бûîļð ţýþé one two three]</string>
    <string name="device_information_android_version">[Åñðŕöîð véŕšîöñ one two]</string>
    <string name="device_information_bootloader_version">[Бööţļöåðéŕ véŕšîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="device_information_brand">[Бŕåñð one]</string>
    <string name="device_information_build_user">[Бûîļð ûšéŕ one two]</string>
    <string name="device_information_clouddpc_version_code">[ᐅ%sᐊ véŕšîöñ çöðé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="device_information_clouddpc_version_name">[ᐅ%sᐊ véŕšîöñ ñåmé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="device_information_device_baseband_version">[Ðévîçé бåšéбåñð véŕšîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="device_information_device_kernel_version">[Ðévîçé ķéŕñéļ véŕšîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="device_information_hardware">[Ĥåŕðŵåŕé one]</string>
    <string name="device_information_manufacturer">[Måñûƒåçţûŕéŕ one two]</string>
    <string name="device_information_model">[Möðéļ one]</string>
    <string name="device_information_pending_system_update_received_time">[Ţîmé ŵĥéñ þéñðîñĝ šýšţém ûþðåţé ŵåš ŕéçéîvéð one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="device_information_security_patch_level">[Šéçûŕîţý þåţçĥ ļévéļ one two three]</string>
    <string name="device_information_serial_number">[Šéŕîåļ ñûmбéŕ one two]</string>
    <string name="device_information_system_update_status">[Šýšţém ûþðåţé šţåţûš one two three]</string>
    <string name="device_information_system_update_status_os_update_available">[ÖŠ ûþðåţé åvåîļåбļé one two three]</string>
    <string name="device_information_system_update_status_security_patch_available">[Šéçûŕîţý þåţçĥ ûþðåţé åvåîļåбļé one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="device_information_system_update_status_unknown_update_available">[Ûþðåţé åvåîļåбļé one two]</string>
    <string name="device_information_system_update_status_up_to_date">[Ûþ ţö ðåţé one two]</string>
    <string name="device_managed">[Ţĥîš ðévîçé îš måñåĝéð бý ᐅ%sᐊ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="device_model_restrictions_block_warning_do">[Ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="device_model_restrictions_block_warning_po">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="device_model_restrictions_incompliant_title">"[ᐅ%1$sᐊ ðévîçéš åŕéñ'ţ åļļöŵéð one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="device_model_restrictions_wipe_warning_do">[Ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="device_model_restrictions_wipe_warning_po">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ бé ŕémövéð. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="device_not_supported_message">[Ýöûŕ šýšţém çåññöţ бé måñåĝéð бý ţĥîš åþþ. Þļéåšé çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ åðmîñîšţŕåţöŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="device_owner_cancel_cancel">[Çåñçéļ one]</string>
    <string name="device_owner_error_ok">[Öķ one]</string>
    <string name="device_owner_reset_device_title">"[Çåñ'ţ šéţ ûþ ðévîçé one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="device_password_title">[Šéţ å šçŕééñ ļöçķ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="device_quota_exceeded_error_message_device_owner">"[Šîñçé ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ ŕéåçĥéð îţš ûšåĝé ļîmîţš, ţĥîš ðévîçé çåñ'ţ бé šéţ ûþ.ññFöŕ ĥéļþ ŵîţĥ šéţûþ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen]"</string>
    <string name="device_quota_exceeded_error_message_profile_owner">"[Šîñçé ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ ŕéåçĥéð îţš ûšåĝé ļîmîţš, ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé çåñ'ţ бé šéţ ûþ.ññFöŕ ĥéļþ ŵîţĥ šéţûþ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty]"</string>
    <string name="device_unmanaged">[Ţĥîš ðévîçé îš ñöţ måñåĝéð. one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="dialog_header_apps_disabled">[Ðîšåбļéð: one two]</string>
    <string name="dialog_header_apps_installed">[Îñšţåļļéð: one two]</string>
    <string name="dialog_header_onc">[Þŕéçöñƒîĝûŕéð Ŵîƒî ñéţŵöŕķš one two three]</string>
    <string name="dialog_title_applications">[Åþþš åvåîļåбļé one two]</string>
    <string name="disable_location_block_warning">"[Îƒ ýöû ðöñ'ţ ţûŕñ öƒƒ ļöçåţîöñ, ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="disable_location_mode_incompliant_title">[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ ðévîçé ļöçåţîöñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="disable_location_wipe_warning">"[Îƒ ýöû ðöñ'ţ ţûŕñ öƒƒ ļöçåţîöñ, ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="dismiss">[Ðîšmîšš one]</string>
    <string name="do_selection_button_text">[Ûšé ƒöŕ ŵöŕķ öñļý one two three four]</string>
    <string name="do_selection_detailed_text">[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ måý бé åбļé ţö šéé ýöûŕ åçţîvîţý åñð ðåţå öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="do_selection_subtitle">[Ŵöŕķ one]</string>
    <string name="done">[Ðöñé one]</string>
    <string name="dont_have_a_code">"[Ðöñ'ţ ĥåvé å çöðé¿ one two three four]"</string>
    <string name="download_qr_dependencies_failed_content">[Ţýþé ţĥé çöðé îñšţéåð one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="download_qr_dependencies_failed_title">[Çåñû2019ţ ðöŵñļöåð QŔ šçåññéŕ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="downloading_administrator_header">[Ĝéţţîñĝ ŕéåðý ƒöŕ ŵöŕķ šéţûþû2026 one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="education_subtext_2">[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ måý бé åбļé ţö šéé ýöûŕ ðåţå åñð åçţîvîţý öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="education_subtext_3">[Åðð ýöûŕ þéŕšöñåļ åççöûñţ ƒîŕšţ ðûŕîñĝ šéţûþ. Åççéšš ţö ŵöŕķ ŕéšöûŕçéš måý бé ļîmîţéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="education_title_1">[Ķééþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš åţ ýöûŕ ƒîñĝéŕţîþš one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="education_title_2">"[Ţĥîš ðévîçé îšñ'ţ þŕîvåţé one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="education_title_3">[Ŕéšéţ ţĥîš ðévîçé ţö šéţ ûþ å ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="enable_location_block_warning">"[Îƒ ýöû ðöñ'ţ ţûŕñ öñ ļöçåţîöñ, ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="enable_location_mode_incompliant_title">[Ţûŕñ öñ ðévîçé ļöçåţîöñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="enable_location_wipe_warning">"[Îƒ ýöû ðöñ'ţ ţûŕñ öñ ļöçåţîöñ, ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="enabled_debug_items">[Éñåбļéð ðéбûĝ îţémš one two three]</string>
    <string name="encrypt">[Éñçŕýþţ one]</string>
    <string name="encrypt_device_text_for_device_owner_setup">[Ţö šéţ ûþ ţĥîš ᐅ%1$sᐊ, îţ ñééðš ţö бé éñçŕýþţéð ƒîŕšţ. Ţĥîš måý ţåķé šömé ţîmé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="encrypt_device_text_for_profile_owner_setup">[Ţö šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé, ýöûŕ ᐅ%1$sᐊ ñééðš ţö бé éñçŕýþţéð. Ţĥîš måý ţåķé šömé ţîmé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="encryption_block_warning_do">"[Îƒ éñçŕýþţîöñ îšñ'ţ ţûŕñéð öñ, ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="encryption_block_warning_po">"[Îƒ éñçŕýþţîöñ îšñ'ţ ţûŕñéð öñ, ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="encryption_incompliant_title">[Ţûŕñ öñ éñçŕýþţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="encryption_policy_desc_secure_startup_required">[Ţĥîš ðévîçé ŕéqûîŕéš šéçûŕé šţåŕţûþ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="encryption_policy_title">[Éñçŕýþţ ýöûŕ ðévîçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="encryption_sufficient">[Éñçŕýþţ ýöûŕ ðévîçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="encryption_wipe_warning_do">"[Îƒ éñçŕýþţîöñ îšñ'ţ ţûŕñéð öñ, ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="encryption_wipe_warning_po">"[Îƒ éñçŕýþţîöñ îšñ'ţ ţûŕñéð öñ, ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ бé ŕémövéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]"</string>
    <string name="end_session_label">[Éñð šéššîöñ one two]</string>
    <string name="ending_user_session">[Éñðîñĝ šéššîöñ… one two]</string>
    <string name="enrollment_token">[Çöðé one]</string>
    <string name="enrollment_token_invalid">[Îñvåļîð çöðé one two]</string>
    <string name="enrollment_token_invalid_characters">[Çöðé mûšţ бé ļéţţéŕš öñļý one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="enrollment_token_invalid_details">[Ţĥé çöðé ýöû ĥåvé þŕövîðéð îšñû2019ţ våļîð. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ, öŕ çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñû2019š åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
    <string name="enrollment_token_invalid_length_signin_et_supported">[Çöðé mûšţ бé 8 öŕ 20 ļéţţéŕš one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="enrollment_token_invalid_length_signin_et_supported_params">[Çöðé mûšţ бé ᐅ%1$dᐊ, ᐅ%2$dᐊ öŕ ᐅ%3$dᐊ ļéţţéŕš one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="ensure_working_environment_manual_update">[Þļéåšé ûþðåţé Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕvîçéš. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="enter_code">[Éñţéŕ çöðé måñûåļļý one two three]</string>
    <string name="enterprise_name_placeholder">[ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="enterprise_not_enrolled_error_message">[Ţö ƒîñîšĥ šéţûþ, éñåбļé ‘ÅñðŕöîðÐévîçéÞöļîçý’ ƒöŕ ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ.ññFöŕ möŕé ðéţåîļš, vîšîţ ĝöö.ĝļ/ñþĥQŽ6. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]</string>
    <string name="error_download_failed">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ ðöŵñļöåð ţĥé åðmîñ åþþ one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="error_hash_mismatch">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ ûšé ţĥé åðmîñ åþþ ðûé ţö å çĥéçķšûm éŕŕöŕ. Föŕ ĥéļþ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]"</string>
    <string name="error_installation_failed">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ îñšţåļļ ţĥé åðmîñ åþþ one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="error_package_invalid">"[Çåñ'ţ ûšé ţĥé åðmîñ åþþ. Îţ'š mîššîñĝ çömþöñéñţš öŕ çöŕŕûþţéð. Föŕ ĥéļþ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="error_wifi">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ çöññéçţ ţö Ŵî-Fî one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="event_details">[Ðéţåîļš one]</string>
    <string name="event_logs">[Évéñţ ļöĝš one two]</string>
    <string name="failed_get_auth_token_title">[Fåîļéð ţö ĝéţ åûţĥéñţîçåţîöñ ţöķéñ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="field_required">[ᐅ%sᐊ îš ŕéqûîŕéð one two three four]</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_cancel_setup_button">[Çåñçéļ šéţûþ one two]</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_accept_header">"[Ļéţ'š šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ ðévîçé one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_permissions_header">[Ýöûŕ åçţîvîţý &amp; ðåţå one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_permissions_secondary_header">[Åþþ þéŕmîššîöñš one two]</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_permissions_secondary_subheader">[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ çåñ šéţ þéŕmîššîöñš ƒöŕ åþþš öñ ţĥîš ᐅ%1$sᐊ, šûçĥ åš mîçŕöþĥöñé, çåméŕå, åñð ļöçåţîöñ þéŕmîššîöñš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_privacy_body">[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ måý бé åбļé ţö šéé ýöûŕ ðåţå åñð åçţîvîţý öñ ţĥîš ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_privacy_title">[Þŕîvåçý ŕémîñðéŕ one two]</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_progress_label">[Šéţţîñĝ ûþ ýöûŕ ðévîçéû2026 one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_return_device_subheader">[Ĝö бåçķ ţö ţĥé þŕévîöûš šçŕééñ, öŕ ŕéšéţ ţĥîš ðévîçé åñð ŕéţûŕñ îţ ţö ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_return_device_title">[Ŕéţûŕñ ţĥîš ðévîçé ţö ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_step_1_header">[Ķééþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš åţ ýöûŕ ƒîñĝéŕţîþš one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_step_2_header">"[Ţĥîš ᐅ%1$sᐊ îšñ'ţ þŕîvåţé one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_step_2_subheader">[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ måý бé åбļé ţö šéé ýöûŕ ðåţå åñð åçţîvîţý öñ ţĥîš ᐅ%1$sᐊ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_provisioning_summary">"[Ûšé ţĥîš ᐅ%1$sᐊ ţö éåšîļý åççéšš ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš. Ţĥîš ᐅ%1$sᐊ îšñ'ţ þŕîvåţé, šö ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ måý бé åбļé ţö šéé ýöûŕ ðåţå åñð åçţîvîţý. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty]"</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_reset_and_return_button">[Ŕéšéţ &amp; ŕéţûŕñ ðévîçé one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="fully_managed_device_with_permission_control_provisioning_summary">[Ûšé ţĥîš ᐅ%1$sᐊ ţö éåšîļý åççéšš ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš. Ţĥîš ᐅ%1$sᐊ îšñ’ţ þŕîvåţé, šö ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ måý бé åбļé ţö šéé ýöûŕ åçţîvîţý åñð ðåţå. Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ çåñ åļšö šéţ þéŕmîššîöñš ƒöŕ åþþš öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé, šûçĥ åš mîçŕöþĥöñé, çåméŕå, åñð ļöçåţîöñ þéŕmîššîöñš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone]</string>
    <string name="future_item_status">[ᐅ%3$s.ᐊ ᐅ Step %1$d of %2$d.ᐊ Îñåçţîvé. one two three four]</string>
    <string name="generic_block_warning_do">[Ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="generic_block_warning_po">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="generic_incompliant_button">[Ĝö ţö šéţţîñĝš one two]</string>
    <string name="generic_incompliant_title">[Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="generic_remove_work_profile_button">[Ŕémövé ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three]</string>
    <string name="generic_wipe_button">[Ŕéšéţ ðévîçé one two]</string>
    <string name="generic_wipe_warning_do">[Ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="generic_wipe_warning_po">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ бé ŕémövéð one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="google_logo">[Ĝööĝļé ļöĝö one two]</string>
    <string name="help_and_feedback_button">[Ĥéļþ &amp; ƒééðбåçķ one two]</string>
    <string name="help_no_code_content_in_new_demo_site">"[Ýöûŕ çöðé îš éîţĥéŕ å ļîñé öƒ ţéxţ öŕ å QŔ çöðé. Îƒ ýöû ðöñ'ţ ĥåvé å çöðé, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. ᐅ"<br/>ᐊ ᐅ<br/>ᐊ Ţö ĝéţ å çöðé ƒöŕ å ðémö, vîšîţ ţĥé &lt;a href=\"https://android.com/enterprise/demo\">Åñðŕöîð Éñţéŕþŕîšé ŵéбšîţé&lt;/a>. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive]</string>
    <string name="hint_locale">[Ļöçåļé one]</string>
    <string name="hint_timezone">[Ţîméžöñé one]</string>
    <string name="if_questions_contact_admin">[Îƒ ýöû ĥåvé qûéšţîöñš, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="indicator_page_number">[Šĥöŵîñĝ þåĝé ᐅ%1$dᐊ öƒ ᐅ%2$dᐊ. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="input_method_block_warning_do">"[Îƒ çûšţöm ķéýбöåŕðš åŕéñ'ţ ţûŕñéð öƒƒ, ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]"</string>
    <string name="input_method_block_warning_po">"[Îƒ çûšţöm ķéýбöåŕðš åŕéñ'ţ ţûŕñéð öƒƒ, ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]"</string>
    <string name="input_method_incompliant_button">[Ŕévîéŵ ķéýбöåŕðš one two]</string>
    <string name="input_method_incompliant_title">[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ çûšţöm ķéýбöåŕðš one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="input_method_wipe_warning_do">"[Îƒ çûšţöm ķéýбöåŕðš åŕéñ'ţ ţûŕñéð öƒƒ, ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]"</string>
    <string name="input_method_wipe_warning_po">"[Îƒ çûšţöm ķéýбöåŕðš åŕéñ'ţ ţûŕñéð öƒƒ, ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ бé ŕémövéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]"</string>
    <string name="install_action_button">[Îñšţåļļ one]</string>
    <string name="install_app_title">[Îñšţåļļîñĝ ñéŵ åþþ… one two three]</string>
    <string name="invalid_token">[Îñvåļîð çöðé one two]</string>
    <string name="invalid_token_details">[Ţĥé çöðé ýöû ĥåvé þŕövîðéð îšñû2019ţ våļîð. Þļéåšé ţŕý åĝåîñ, öŕ çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñû2019š åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]</string>
    <string name="just_a_sec">[Ĵûšţ å šéç… one two]</string>
    <string name="launcher_app_cant_be_used_by_work_profile">"[Ţĥîš ļåûñçĥéŕ åþþ çåñ'ţ бé ûšéð бý ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="launcher_label">[Ķîöšķ Ļåûñçĥéŕ one two]</string>
    <string name="learn_more_admin_demo">[Ðémö ƒöŕ ÎŢ åðmîñš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="learn_more_admin_demo_in_new_site_description">[ÎŢ åðmîñš šĥöûļð ûšé ţĥîš åþþ ŵîţĥ ţĥé Åñðŕöîð Éñţéŕþŕîšé ðémö. Ţö ĝéţ ţĥé çöðé ƒöŕ å ðémö, vîšîţ ţĥé &lt;a href=\"https://android.com/enterprise/demo\">Åñðŕöîð Éñţéŕþŕîšé ŵéбšîţé&lt;/a>. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty]</string>
    <string name="learn_more_clouddpc_description">[ᐅ%sᐊ ĥéļþš ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ķééþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ ðåţå šéçûŕé. Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ çåñ ûšé ţĥîš åþþ ţö måñåĝé šéçûŕîţý þöļîçîéš åñð šéţţîñĝš öñ ýöûŕ ðévîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone]</string>
    <string name="learn_more_enroll_device">[Éñŕöļļ ýöûŕ ðévîçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="learn_more_enroll_device_description">"[Ţö ûšé ţĥîš åþþ, éñţéŕ ţĥé çöðé þŕövîðéð бý ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. Ţĥîš måý бé å ļîñé öƒ ţéxţ öŕ å QŔ çöðé. Îƒ ýöû ðöñ'ţ ĥåvé å çöðé, åšķ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree]"</string>
    <string name="learn_more_get_started">[Ĝéţ šţåŕţéð one two]</string>
    <string name="locale_title">[Ļöçåļé one]</string>
    <string name="location_mode_disable_title">[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ ðévîçé ļöçåţîöñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="location_mode_enable_title">[Ţûŕñ öñ ðévîçé ļöçåţîöñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="lost_mode_call_owner">Call owner</string>
    <string name="lost_mode_emergency">Emergency</string>
    <string name="lost_mode_found_device">I found this device</string>
    <string name="lost_mode_header">This device was reported lost</string>
    <string name="lost_mode_location_shared_content">[Ýöûŕ ļöçåţîöñ ŵåš šĥåŕéð ŵîţĥ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. Föŕ möŕé îñƒöŕmåţîöñ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="lost_mode_lost_content">"[Îƒ ýöû ðöñ'ţ ţĥîñķ ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵåš ļöšţ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="lost_mode_lost_title">[Ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵåš ŕéþöŕţéð ļöšţ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="lost_mode_my_device">This is my device</string>
    <string name="lost_mode_organization_and_street_address">%1$s, %2$s</string>
    <string name="lost_mode_unlock">Unlock</string>
    <string name="managed_device_info">[Måñåĝéð ðévîçé îñƒö one two three]</string>
    <string name="managed_provisioning_error_text">"[Çöûļðñ'ţ šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ ðéþåŕţméñţ öŕ ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]"</string>
    <string name="max_days_with_work_off_blocked_description">[Ýöûŕ þéŕšöñåļ åþþš åŕé бļöçķéð ûñţîļ ýöû ţûŕñ öñ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="max_days_with_work_off_notification_button">[Ţûŕñ öñ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="max_days_with_work_off_resolution_failed_description">[Þéŕšöñåļ åþþš ŵîļļ šţåý бļöçķéð ûñţîļ ýöû çöññéçţ ţö ţĥé îñţéŕñéţ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="max_days_with_work_off_resolution_failed_long_title">[Çĥéçķ ýöûŕ îñţéŕñéţ çöññéçţîöñ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="max_days_with_work_off_resolution_failed_short_title">"[Çåñ'ţ çöññéçţ ţö ţĥé îñţéŕñéţ one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="max_days_with_work_off_resolution_in_progress_title">[Šýñçîñĝ þöļîçîéš… one two three]</string>
    <string name="max_days_with_work_off_retry_button">[Ţŕý åĝåîñ one two]</string>
    <string name="max_days_with_work_off_title">[Ţûŕñ öñ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="max_days_with_work_off_warning_description">[Ýöûŕ þéŕšöñåļ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð ţömöŕŕöŵ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="max_security_patch_age_days_block_warning_do">[Ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð šööñ бéçåûšé ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ñö ļöñĝéŕ šûþþöŕţš ţĥîš Åñðŕöîð véŕšîöñ. Çĥéçķ ƒöŕ ûþðåţéš öŕ çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone]</string>
    <string name="max_security_patch_age_days_block_warning_po">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð šööñ бéçåûšé ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ñö ļöñĝéŕ šûþþöŕţš ţĥîš Åñðŕöîð véŕšîöñ. Çĥéçķ ƒöŕ ûþðåţéš öŕ çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone]</string>
    <string name="max_security_patch_age_days_incompliant_button">[Çĥéçķ ƒöŕ ûþðåţéš. one two three]</string>
    <string name="max_security_patch_age_days_incompliant_title">[Ţĥîš Åñðŕöîð véŕšîöñ îš ñö ļöñĝéŕ šûþþöŕţéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="max_security_patch_age_days_wipe_warning_do">[Ýöûŕ ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð šööñ бéçåûšé ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ñö ļöñĝéŕ šûþþöŕţš ţĥîš Åñðŕöîð véŕšîöñ. Çĥéçķ ƒöŕ ûþðåţéš öŕ çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone]</string>
    <string name="max_security_patch_age_days_wipe_warning_po">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ бé ðéļéţéð šööñ бéçåûšé ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ñö ļöñĝéŕ šûþþöŕţš ţĥîš Åñðŕöîð véŕšîöñ. Çĥéçķ ƒöŕ ûþðåţéš öŕ çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo]</string>
    <string name="may_take_a_few_minutes">[Ţĥîš måý ţåķé å ƒéŵ mîñûţéš one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="message_profile_setup_failed">[Ţö ĥéļþ ûš ûñðéŕšţåñð ŵĥåţ ŵéñţ ŵŕöñĝ, šéñð ƒééðбåçķ бéƒöŕé ţŕýîñĝ åĝåîñ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="min_security_patch_date_block_warning_do">[Ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð šööñ бéçåûšé ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ñö ļöñĝéŕ šûþþöŕţš ţĥîš Åñðŕöîð véŕšîöñ. Çĥéçķ ƒöŕ ûþðåţéš öŕ çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone]</string>
    <string name="min_security_patch_date_block_warning_po">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð šööñ бéçåûšé ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ñö ļöñĝéŕ šûþþöŕţš ţĥîš Åñðŕöîð véŕšîöñ. Çĥéçķ ƒöŕ ûþðåţéš öŕ çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone]</string>
    <string name="min_security_patch_date_incompliant_button">[Ûþðåţé ðévîçé one two]</string>
    <string name="min_security_patch_date_incompliant_title">[Ûþðåţé ţĥîš ðévîçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="min_security_patch_date_wipe_warning_do">[Ýöûŕ ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð šööñ бéçåûšé ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ñö ļöñĝéŕ šûþþöŕţš ţĥîš Åñðŕöîð véŕšîöñ. Çĥéçķ ƒöŕ ûþðåţéš öŕ çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone]</string>
    <string name="min_security_patch_date_wipe_warning_po">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ бé ðéļéţéð šööñ бéçåûšé ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ñö ļöñĝéŕ šûþþöŕţš ţĥîš Åñðŕöîð véŕšîöñ. Çĥéçķ ƒöŕ ûþðåţéš öŕ çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo]</string>
    <string name="minimum_api_level_block_warning_do">[Ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="minimum_api_level_block_warning_po">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="minimum_api_level_incompliant_title">"[Åñðŕöîð ᐅ%1$sᐊ îšñ'ţ åļļöŵéð one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="minimum_api_level_wipe_warning_do">[Ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="minimum_api_level_wipe_warning_po">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ бé ŕémövéð. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="navigation_button_description">[Ñåvîĝåţé ûþ one two]</string>
    <string name="network_error_alert_dialog_title">[Ñéţŵöŕķ éŕŕöŕ one two]</string>
    <string name="network_error_dialog_setup_wifi">[Šéţ ûþ ŴîFî one two]</string>
    <string name="network_error_message">[Ŕéçöññéçţ ţö å möбîļé öŕ ŴÎ-FÎ ñéţŵöŕķ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="network_error_setup_do">[Ýöû ñééð å ŵöŕķîñĝ îñţéŕñéţ çöññéçţîöñ ţö šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ðévîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="network_error_setup_po">[Ýöû ñééð å ŵöŕķîñĝ îñţéŕñéţ çöññéçţîöñ ţö šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="network_error_title">[Ñö çöññéçţîöñ one two]</string>
    <string name="new_enrollment_token_created">[Ñéŵ éñŕöļļméñţ ţöķéñ ĥåš бééñ çŕéåţéð. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="next">[Ñéxţ one]</string>
    <string name="nfc_comment">[ÑFÇ þŕövîšîöñîñĝ one two]</string>
    <string name="nfc_dialog_submit">[Šåvé one]</string>
    <string name="no_connection_dialog_message">"[Îƒ ýöû ðöñ'ţ çöññéçţ ţö Ŵî-Fî ţö ûþðåţé ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ'š þöļîçîéš, ýöû måý ñöţ бé åбļé ţö ûšé ţĥîš ðévîçé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen]"</string>
    <string name="no_connection_dialog_title">"[Ðöñ'ţ çöññéçţ ţö Ŵî-Fî¿ one two three four five]"</string>
    <string name="no_network_connection_details">[Þļéåšé çĥéçķ ýöûŕ îñţéŕñéţ çöññéçţîöñ åñð ţŕý åĝåîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="no_network_connection_title">[Ñö ñéţŵöŕķ çöññéçţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="no_preferable_camera_found">[Ñö þŕéƒéŕåбļé çåméŕå ƒöûñð, šŵîţçĥîñĝ ţö ţéxţ îñþûţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="non_compliance_reason_admin_type">[Ţĥé åðmîñ ţýþé ðöéš ñöţ šûþþöŕţ ţĥîš þöļîçý one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="non_compliance_reason_api_level">[Ţĥé çûŕŕéñţ Åñðŕöîð ÅÞÎ véŕšîöñ ðöéš ñöţ šûþþöŕţ ţĥîš þöļîçý one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="non_compliance_reason_app_not_installed">[Å ŕéqûîŕéð åþþ ĥåš ñöţ бééñ îñšţåļļéð one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="non_compliance_reason_invalid_value">[Ţĥîš þöļîçý ĥåš åñ îñvåļîð våļûé one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="non_compliance_reason_unsupported">[Ţĥîš þöļîçý îš ñöţ šûþþöŕţéð бý ţĥîš véŕšîöñ öƒ ÐÞÇ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_compliance_description">[Çömþļîåñçé-ŕéļåţéð ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_compliance_name">[Çömþļîåñçé one two]</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_lost_mode_description">[Ļöšţ möðé-ŕéļåţéð ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš one two three four]</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_lost_mode_name">[Ļöšţ möðé one two]</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_setup_description">[Šéţûþ-ŕéļåţéð ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš one two three]</string>
    <string name="notification_channel_setup_name">[Šéţûþ one]</string>
    <string name="organization_admin">[ÎŢ åðmîñ one]</string>
    <string name="overflow_policy_pull">[Šýñç þöļîçîéš one two]</string>
    <string name="password_block_warning_do">"[Îƒ å ñéŵ šçŕééñ ļöçķ îšñ'ţ šéţ, ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="password_block_warning_po">"[Îƒ å ñéŵ šçŕééñ ļöçķ îšñ'ţ šéţ, ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="password_expiring_content">[Ýöûŕ þåššŵöŕð îš åбöûţ ţö éxþîŕé, þļéåšé çĥåñĝé îţ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="password_expiring_title">[Ýöûŕ þåššŵöŕð îš éxþîŕîñĝ šööñ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="password_incompliant_button">[Šéţ šçŕééñ ļöçķ one two]</string>
    <string name="password_incompliant_title">[Šéţ å ñéŵ šçŕééñ ļöçķ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="password_required_title">[Šéţ å šçŕééñ ļöçķ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="password_unchanged">[ûñçĥåñĝéð one two]</string>
    <string name="password_wipe_warning_do">"[Îƒ å ñéŵ šçŕééñ ļöçķ îšñ'ţ šéţ, ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="password_wipe_warning_po">"[Îƒ å ñéŵ šçŕééñ ļöçķ îšñ'ţ šéţ, ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ бé ŕémövéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]"</string>
    <string name="past_item_status">[ᐅ%3$s.ᐊ ᐅ Step %1$d of %2$d.ᐊ Çömþļéţé. one two three four]</string>
    <string name="pending_policy_title">"[Çåñ'ţ ƒîñîšĥ šéţûþ one two three]"</string>
    <string name="permitted_accessibility_services_desc">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ðöéšñ'ţ åļļöŵ ţĥéšé åççéššîбîļîţý šéŕvîçéš: one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="permitted_accessibility_services_specifc_desc">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ðöéšñ'ţ åļļöŵ çûšţöm åççéššîбîļîţý šéŕvîçéš öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]"</string>
    <string name="permitted_accessibility_services_specifc_title">[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three]</string>
    <string name="permitted_accessibility_services_title">[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ åççéššîбîļîţý šéŕvîçéš one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="permitted_input_methods_desc">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ðöéšñ'ţ åļļöŵ ţĥéšé ķéýбöåŕðš: one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="permitted_input_methods_specifc_desc">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ðöéšñ'ţ åļļöŵ çûšţöm ķéýбöåŕðš öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="permitted_input_methods_specifc_title">[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three]</string>
    <string name="permitted_input_methods_title">[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ çûšţöm ķéýбöåŕðš one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="personal_usage_disallowed_details">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ðöéšñ'ţ åļļöŵ å ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="personal_usage_disallowed_title">"[Çåñ'ţ šéţ ûþ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="pick_launcher">[Öķ one]</string>
    <string name="po_selection_button_text">[Ûšé ƒöŕ ŵöŕķ &amp; þéŕšöñåļ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="po_selection_detailed_text">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš åŕé ķéþţ îñ å ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé. Ðåţå îñ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé îš vîšîбļé ţö ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]</string>
    <string name="po_selection_subtitle">[Ŵöŕķ &amp; þéŕšöñåļ ûšé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="policy_apps_list_activity_title">[Ŵöŕķ åþþš one two]</string>
    <string name="policy_error_device_owner_message">"[Ţĥîš ðévîçé çåñ'ţ бé šéţ ûþ åñð ñééðš ţö бé ŕéšéţ.ñFöŕ ĥéļþ ŵîţĥ šéţûþ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_block_warning_do_other">[Ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð îñ ᐅ%1$dᐊ ðåýš one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_block_warning_do_today">[Ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð ţöðåý one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_block_warning_do_tomorrow">[Ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð ţömöŕŕöŵ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_block_warning_po_other">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð îñ ᐅ%1$dᐊ ðåýš one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_block_warning_po_today">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð ţöðåý one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_block_warning_po_tomorrow">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð ţömöŕŕöŵ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_close">[Çļöšé one]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_contact_your_it_admin">[Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_error_details">[Éŕŕöŕ îñƒö one two]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_error_info">[Šĥöŵ éŕŕöŕ îñƒö one two]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_multiple_action_block_warning_do">"[Îƒ ţĥéšé šéţţîñĝš åŕéñ'ţ ûþðåţéð, ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_multiple_action_block_warning_po">"[Îƒ ţĥéšé šéţţîñĝš åŕéñ'ţ ûþðåţéð, ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]"</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_multiple_action_do">[Ûþðåţé ðévîçé šéţţîñĝš one two three]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_multiple_action_po">[Ûþðåţé ðévîçé šéţţîñĝš one two three]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_multiple_action_wipe_warning_do">"[Îƒ ţĥéšé šéţţîñĝš åŕéñ'ţ ûþðåţéð, ýöûŕ ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_multiple_action_wipe_warning_po">"[Îƒ ţĥéšé šéţţîñĝš åŕéñ'ţ ûþðåţéð, ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ бé ŕémövéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]"</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_notification_content">"[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ĥåvé бééñ ŕémövéð. Ţåþ ţö ŕévîéŵ ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ'š þöļîçîéš. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]"</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_notification_title">[Þöļîçý îñçömþļîåñţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_tap_to_fix">[Ţåþ ţö ƒîx one two]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_unblock_apps_do">[Ûñбļöçķ ýöûŕ åþþš one two three]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_unblock_apps_po">[Ûñбļöçķ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_wipe_warning_do_other">[Ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð îñ ᐅ%1$dᐊ ðåýš one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_wipe_warning_do_today">[Ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð ţöðåý one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_wipe_warning_do_tomorrow">[Ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð ţömöŕŕöŵ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_wipe_warning_po_other">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ бé ŕémövéð îñ ᐅ%1$dᐊ ðåýš one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_wipe_warning_po_today">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ бé ŕémövéð ţöðåý one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="policy_incompliant_wipe_warning_po_tomorrow">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ бé ŕémövéð ţömöŕŕöŵ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="policy_name">[Þöļîçý ñåmé one two]</string>
    <string name="policy_not_supported_desc">[Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="policy_not_supported_title">"[Ŵöŕķ þöļîçý îšñ'ţ šûþþöŕţéð one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="policy_pull_dialog_message">[Þöļîçîéš åŕé бéîñĝ åþþļîéð… one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="policy_pull_title">[Šýñçîñĝ þöļîçîéš… one two three]</string>
    <string name="policy_sync_block_warning_do">"[Îƒ þöļîçîéš åŕéñ'ţ šýñçéð, ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="policy_sync_block_warning_po">"[Îƒ þöļîçîéš åŕéñ'ţ šýñçéð, ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="policy_sync_incompliant_button">[Ĝö ţö Ŵî-Fî šéţţîñĝš one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="policy_sync_incompliant_title_do">"[Šýñç ţĥîš ðévîçé'š þöļîçîéš one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="policy_sync_incompliant_title_po">[Šýñç ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þöļîçîéš one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="policy_sync_wipe_warning_do">"[Îƒ þöļîçîéš åŕéñ'ţ šýñçéð, ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]"</string>
    <string name="policy_sync_wipe_warning_po">"[Îƒ þöļîçîéš åŕéñ'ţ šýñçéð, ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ бé ŕémövéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]"</string>
    <string name="policy_version">[Þöļîçý véŕšîöñ one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_about_this_device_category_header">[Åбöûţ ţĥîš ðévîçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_about_this_device_category_header_work_profile">[Åбöûţ ţĥîš ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_already_enabled_debug_items">[Ðéбûĝ îţémš åŕé åļŕéåðý öñ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_android_build_number">[Åñðŕöîð бûîļð ñûmбéŕ one two three]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_android_build_type">[Åñðŕöîð бûîļð ţýþé one two three]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_android_version">[Åñðŕöîð véŕšîöñ one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_bootloader_version">[Бööţļöåðéŕ véŕšîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_brand">[Бŕåñð one]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_build_user">[Бûîļð ûšéŕ one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_clouddpc_version_code">[ᐅ%sᐊ véŕšîöñ çöðé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_clouddpc_version_name">[ᐅ%sᐊ véŕšîöñ ñåmé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_device_baseband_version">[Ðévîçé бåšéбåñð véŕšîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_device_kernel_version">[Ðévîçé ķéŕñéļ véŕšîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_hardware">[Ĥåŕðŵåŕé one]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_manufacturer">[Måñûƒåçţûŕéŕ one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_model">[Möðéļ one]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_pending_system_update_received_time">[Ţîmé ŵĥéñ þéñðîñĝ šýšţém ûþðåţé ŵåš ŕéçéîvéð one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_security_patch_level">[Šéçûŕîţý þåţçĥ ļévéļ one two three]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_serial_number">[Šéŕîåļ ñûmбéŕ one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_system_update_status">[Šýšţém ûþðåţé šţåţûš one two three]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_system_update_status_os_update_available">[ÖŠ ûþðåţé åvåîļåбļé one two three]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_system_update_status_security_patch_available">[Šéçûŕîţý þåţçĥ ûþðåţé åvåîļåбļé one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_system_update_status_unknown_update_available">[Ûþðåţé åvåîļåбļé one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_device_information_system_update_status_up_to_date">[Ûþ ţö ðåţé one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_enabled_debug_items">[Ðéбûĝ îţémš åŕé öñ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_entry_default_sync_time">[Ñöţ šýñçéð one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_entry_non_compliance_button">[Ûþðåţé šéţţîñĝš one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_entry_non_compliance_title">[Ûþðåţé ðévîçé šéţţîñĝš one two three]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_entry_sync_error">"[Çåñ'ţ šýñç þöļîçîéš. Ţŕý åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ. one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_entry_sync_time_absolute">[Šýñçéð åţ ᐅ%1$sᐊ öñ ᐅ%2$sᐊ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_entry_sync_time_relative">[Šýñçéð ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_entry_title">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ ðévîçé one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_entry_title_work_profile">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_help_and_support_entry">[Ĥéļþ &amp; ƒééðбåçķ one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_licences_entry">[Ļîçéñšéš one]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_overflow_all_policies">[Vîéŵ þöļîçîéš one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_overflow_debug_mode">[Ðéбûĝ one]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_overflow_event_logs">[Évéñţ ļöĝš one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_overflow_sync_policy">[Šýñç þöļîçîéš one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_policy_details_title">[Þöļîçîéš ţĥåţ åƒƒéçţ ýöûŕ ðévîçé one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_policy_details_title_work_profile">[Þöļîçîéš ţĥåţ åƒƒéçţ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_policy_name">[Þöļîçý ñåmé one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_policy_version">[Þöļîçý véŕšîöñ one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_status_compliance_rules">[Çömþļîåñçé ŕûļéš one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_support_and_details_category_header">[Ðévîçé šûþþöŕţ one two]</string>
    <string name="privacy_hub_support_and_details_category_header_work_profile">[Ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé šûþþöŕţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="profile_managed">[Ţĥîš þŕöƒîļé îš måñåĝéð бý ᐅ%sᐊ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="profile_owner_cancel_cancel">[Ñö one]</string>
    <string name="profile_owner_cancel_message">[Šţöþ šéţţîñĝ ûþ¿ one two]</string>
    <string name="profile_owner_cancel_ok">[Ýéš one]</string>
    <string name="profile_password_desc">[Ţĥîš ļöçķ þŕöţéçţš ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ ðåţå öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="profile_password_title">[Šéţ å ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ļöçķ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="qr_enter_code_description">[Éñţéŕ çöðé ƒŕöm ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="qr_hint_enter_code">[Çöðé one]</string>
    <string name="qr_scan_activity_title">[Þļéåšé þöîñţ ýöûŕ ðévîçé ţö ţĥé šçŕééñ ţö çåþţûŕé QŔ çöðé, öŕ éñţéŕ ţĥé çöðé måñûåļļý. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="qr_scan_code">[Šçåñ çöðé one two]</string>
    <string name="qr_scanner_open">[Öþéñ one]</string>
    <string name="qr_scanner_ready">[QŔ šçåññéŕ îš ŕéåðý one two three four]</string>
    <string name="qr_tutorial_details">[Šçåñ öŕ éñţéŕ ţĥé çöðé þŕövîðéð бý ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten]</string>
    <string name="qr_tutorial_title">[Éñŕöļļ ţĥîš ðévîçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="readable_action_disable_location">[Ţö ûšé ţĥîš ðévîçé, ţûŕñ öƒƒ ļöçåţîöñ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="readable_action_enable_location">[Ţö ûšé ţĥîš ðévîçé, ţûŕñ öñ ļöçåţîöñ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="readable_action_encryption_password_required">[Ţûŕñ öñ šéçûŕé šţåŕţ-ûþ, ţĥéñ šéţ å ÞÎÑ, þåţţéŕñ, öŕ þåššŵöŕð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="readable_action_password_required">[Åðð å ÞÎÑ, þåţţéŕñ, öŕ þåššŵöŕð, ţĥéñ ţûŕñ öñ šéçûŕé šţåŕţ-ûþ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="readable_action_system_update">[Ţåþ ţö ĝéţ šţåŕţéð one two three four]</string>
    <string name="readable_app_usage_permission_requirements">[Ţûŕñ öñ åþþ þéŕmîššîöñ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_accessibility_services">[Ðîšåбļé çéŕţåîñ åççéššîбîļîţý šéŕvîçéš one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_add_user_disabled">[Åððîñĝ å ûšéŕ îš ðîšåбļéð one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_adjust_volume_disabled">[Åûðîö îš ðîšåбļéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_camera_disabled">[Çåméŕå îš ðîšåбļéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_cross_profile_copy_paste_disabled">[Çöþýîñĝ åñð þåšţîñĝ бéţŵééñ ŵöŕķ åñð þéŕšöñåļ þŕöƒîļéš îš ðîšåбļéð one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_debugging_features_disabled">[Ðéбûĝĝîñĝ ƒéåţûŕéš åŕé ðîšåбļéð one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_encryption_password">[Éñçŕýþţ ýöûŕ ðévîçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_encryption_required_title">[Éñçŕýþţ ýöûŕ ðévîçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_encryption_secure_start_up">[Ţĥîš ðévîçé ŕéqûîŕéš šéçûŕé šţåŕţ-ûþ one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_encryption_unencrypted">[Éñçŕýþţ ýöûŕ ðévîçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_encryption_unencrypted_and_no_password">[Éñçŕýþţ ýöûŕ ðévîçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_factory_reset_disabled">[Fåçţöŕý ŕéšéţţîñĝ ţĥé ðévîçé îš ðîšåбļéð one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_input_methods">[Ðîšåбļé çéŕţåîñ ķéýбöåŕðš one two three]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_keyguard_disabled">[Ķéýĝûåŕð îš ðîšåбļéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_modify_accounts_disabled">[Åððîñĝ åñð ŕémövîñĝ åççöûñţš åŕé ðîšåбļéð one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_mount_physical_media_disabled">[Möûñţîñĝ þĥýšîçåļ méðîå îš ðîšåбļéð one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_onc">[Öþéñ ñéţŵöŕķ çöñƒîĝûŕåţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_printing_disabled">[Þŕîñţîñĝ îš ðîšåбļéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_remove_user_disabled">[Ŕémövîñĝ å ûšéŕ îš ðîšåбļéð one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_safe_boot_disabled">[Šåƒé бööţ îš ðîšåбļéð one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_screen_capture_disabled">[Šçŕééñ çåþţûŕé îš ðîšåбļéð one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_status_bar_disabled">[Šţåţûš бåŕ îš ðîšåбļéð one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="readable_name_system_update">[Šýšţém ûþðåţé ŕéqûîŕéð one two three]</string>
    <string name="remote_password_reset_title">[Çöñƒîŕm ýöûŕ šçŕééñ ļöçķ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="request_enrollment_token_message">[Éñŕöļļméñţ ţöķéñ îš бéîñĝ ŕéqûéšţéð. one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="reset">[Ŕéšéţ one]</string>
    <string name="reset_confirmation">[Åŕé ýöû šûŕé¿ one two]</string>
    <string name="reset_device">[Ŕéšéţ ðévîçé one two]</string>
    <string name="reset_device_message">[Ðåţå öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="reset_device_title">[Ŕéšéţ ðévîçé¿ one two]</string>
    <string name="reset_message">"[Ţĥîš ŵîļļ éŕåšé åļļ ðåţå ƒŕöm ýöûŕ ðévîçé'š îñţéŕñåļ šţöŕåĝé. Ţĥîš åçţîöñ çåñ ñöţ бé ûñðöñé. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="restore_title_v2">[Бåçķ ûþ &amp; ŕéšţöŕé ŵöŕķ ðåţå one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="retry">[Ţŕý åĝåîñ one two]</string>
    <string name="section_content">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ šéçţîöñ çöñţéñţ: ᐅ%2$sᐊ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="section_heading">[ᐅ%1$sᐊ šéçţîöñ ĥéåðîñĝ. one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="security_check_failed_title">"[Ţĥîš ðévîçé çåñ'ţ þåšš šéçûŕîţý çĥéçķš one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="security_tutorial_details">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé çöñţåîñš åļļ öƒ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš åñð îš ķéþţ šéçûŕé бý ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="security_tutorial_title">[Šéþåŕåţé ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ &amp; þéŕšöñåļ ðåţå one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="selection_divider_text">[öŕ one]</string>
    <string name="selector_title">[Ĥöŵ ŵîļļ ýöû ûšé ţĥîš ðévîçé¿ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="set_up_app_action_button">[Šéţ ûþ one]</string>
    <string name="set_up_screen_lock_action_button">[Šéţ ûþ one]</string>
    <string name="setup_action_cancel_setup_message">"[Ţĥîš ðévîçé çåñ'ţ бé šéţ ûþ åñð ñééðš ţö бé çåñçéļļéð.ñFöŕ ĥéļþ ŵîţĥ šéţûþ, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen]"</string>
    <string name="setup_action_default_description">[Ţö ƒîñîšĥ ŵöŕķ šéţûþ, öþéñ ţĥé åþþ ƒŕöm ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ åñð ƒöļļöŵ ţĥé îñšţŕûçţîöñš one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen]</string>
    <string name="setup_action_default_title">[Öþéñ åþþ ƒŕöm ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="setup_action_default_title_with_app_name">[Šéţ ûþ ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three]</string>
    <string name="setup_applying_policies">"[Åþþļýîñĝ ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ'š þöļîçîéš one two three four five six seven eight]"</string>
    <string name="setup_complete_title">[Ýöûŕ ðévîçé îš ŕéåðý ţö ĝö¡ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="setup_device">[Šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="setup_device_encryption">[Šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ᐅ%1$sᐊ. Éñçŕýþţîöñ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="setup_device_progress">[Šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ᐅ%1$sᐊ. Šĥöŵîñĝ þŕöĝŕéšš one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="setup_downloading_chrome">[Ðöŵñļöåðîñĝ Çĥŕömé: ᐅ%1$dᐊ%% one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="setup_downloading_play_service">[Ðöŵñļöåðîñĝ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕvîçéš: ᐅ%1$dᐊ%% one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="setup_downloading_play_store">[Ðöŵñļöåðîñĝ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý Šţöŕé: ᐅ%1$dᐊ%% one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="setup_experience_title">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ çĥéçķļîšţ one two three]</string>
    <string name="setup_getting_info">[Ĝéţţîñĝ åççöûñţ îñƒö… one two three]</string>
    <string name="setup_installing_chrome">[Ûþðåţîñĝ Çĥŕömé one two]</string>
    <string name="setup_installing_play_services">[Ûþðåţîñĝ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý šéŕvîçéš one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="setup_installing_play_store">[Ûþðåţîñĝ Ĝööĝļé Þļåý Šţöŕé one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="setup_preinstalling_apps">[Îñšţåļļîñĝ åþþš… one two]</string>
    <string name="setup_profile">[Šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ þŕöƒîļé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="setup_profile_encryption">[Šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ þŕöƒîļé. Éñçŕýþţîöñ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="setup_profile_progress">[Šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ þŕöƒîļé. Šĥöŵîñĝ þŕöĝŕéšš one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="setup_registering_device">[Ŕéĝîšţéŕîñĝ ðévîçé… one two three]</string>
    <string name="setup_registering_profile">[Ŕéĝîšţéŕîñĝ þŕöƒîļé… one two three]</string>
    <string name="setup_setting_up_work_profile">[Šéţţîñĝ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé… one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="setup_updating_play_services">[Ûþðåţîñĝ ðévîçé… one two]</string>
    <string name="setup_updating_play_services_finishing">[Fîñîšĥîñĝ ûþðåţîñĝ ðévîçé one two three]</string>
    <string name="setup_work_device">[Šéţţîñĝ ûþ ŵöŕķ ðévîçéû2026 one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="setup_work_profile">[Šéţ ûþ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="sign_in">[Šîĝñ îñ one]</string>
    <string name="skip">[Šķîþ one]</string>
    <string name="start_action_button">[Šţåŕţ one]</string>
    <string name="starting_new_user_session">[Šţåŕţîñĝ šéššîöñ… one two three]</string>
    <string name="status_activity_device_information_text_new">[Ţĥéšé åŕé ţĥé ðéţåîļš ýöûŕ åðmîñ çåñ vîéŵ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="status_activity_no_network_snackbar">[Ñö ñéţŵöŕķ çöññéçţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="status_activity_overflow_all_policies">[Åļļ þöļîçîéš one two]</string>
    <string name="status_activity_overflow_debug_mode">[Ðéбûĝ one]</string>
    <string name="status_activity_overflow_device_details">[Ðévîçé ðéţåîļš one two]</string>
    <string name="status_activity_overflow_device_details_title">[Ðévîçé ðéţåîļš one two]</string>
    <string name="status_activity_overflow_help_and_feedback">[Ĥéļþ &amp; ƒééðбåçķ one two]</string>
    <string name="status_activity_overflow_licences">[Ļîçéñçéš one]</string>
    <string name="status_activity_policies">[Þöļîçîéš one]</string>
    <string name="status_activity_policy_error_snackbar">[Éŕŕöŕ ûþðåţîñĝ þöļîçîéš one two three]</string>
    <string name="status_compliance_rules">[Çömþļîåñçé ŕûļéš one two]</string>
    <string name="step_quarantined_mode_delay">[Ţĥîš måý ţåķé å ƒéŵ mîñûţéš one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="stop_setup_reset_device_question">[Šţöþ šéţûþ &amp; ŕéšéţ ᐅ%1$sᐊ¿ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="switch_camera">[Šŵîţçĥ Çåméŕå one two]</string>
    <string name="switch_to_work_profile_option">[Šéţ ûþ åñöţĥéŕ ŵåý one two three four]</string>
    <string name="sync_time">[Ļåšţ šýñçéð: ᐅ%1$sᐊ öñ ᐅ%2$sᐊ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="syncing_now">[Šýñçîñĝ ñöŵ… one two]</string>
    <string name="terms">[Ţéŕmš one]</string>
    <string name="text_et_input_activity_title">[Šçåñ öŕ éñţéŕ çöðé one two three four]</string>
    <string name="this_will_reset_take_back_first_screen">[Ţĥîš ŵîļļ ŕéšéţ ýöûŕ ᐅ%1$sᐊ åñð ţåķé ýöû бåçķ ţö ţĥé ƒîŕšţ šçŕééñ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="time_date">[ᐅ%2$sᐊ, ᐅ%1$sᐊ one two]</string>
    <string name="timezone_title">[Ţîmé žöñé one two]</string>
    <string name="title_profile_setup_failed">"[Çåñ'ţ šéţ ûþ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="trampoline_label">[Šţåŕţîñĝ ķîöšķ åþþ… one two three]</string>
    <string name="trampoline_launch_failure">"[Çåñ'ţ öþéñ åþþ. Ţŕý ŕéšţåŕţîñĝ ýöûŕ ðévîçé. one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="transient_error_message">[Šömé ţéçĥñîçåļ îššûéš åŕé þŕévéñţîñĝ šéţûþ ŕîĝĥţ ñöŵ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="transient_error_title">[Ţŕý šéţûþ åĝåîñ ļåţéŕ one two three four five]</string>
    <string name="try_again">[Ţŕý åĝåîñ one two]</string>
    <string name="turn_off_action_button">[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ one]</string>
    <string name="turn_off_location_action_button">[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ one]</string>
    <string name="turn_off_work_details">"[Ţö þåûšé ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš åñð ñöţîƒîçåţîöñš, ţûŕñ öƒƒ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé îñ Šéţţîñĝš. Ŵĥéñ ýöû'ŕé ŕéåðý ţö ûšé ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš, ĵûšţ ţûŕñ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé бåçķ öñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree]"</string>
    <string name="turn_off_work_title">"[Ţûŕñ öƒƒ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵĥéñ ýöû'ŕé ðöñé one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="turn_on_location_action_button">[Ţûŕñ öñ one]</string>
    <string name="unrecoverable_error_detailed">"[Ñöţ åļļ þöļîçîéš çöûļð бé åþþļîéð öñ ţĥîš ðévîçé. Þļéåšé çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ öŕĝåñîžåţîöñ'š åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen]"</string>
    <string name="untrusted_os_policy_block_warning_do">[Ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="untrusted_os_policy_block_warning_po">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="untrusted_os_policy_compromised_os_incompliant_block_warning_do_desc">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ðöéšñ'ţ åļļöŵ ŵöŕķ ðåţå öñ ðévîçéš ŵîţĥ çömþŕömîšéð šéçûŕîţý, šûçĥ åš ŕööţéð ðévîçéš. Ŕéšéţ ţĥîš ðévîçé ţö ƒåçţöŕý šéţţîñĝš. ññ• Ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð. ñ• Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight]"</string>
    <string name="untrusted_os_policy_compromised_os_incompliant_block_warning_po_desc">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ðöéšñ'ţ åļļöŵ ŵöŕķ ðåţå öñ ðévîçéš ŵîţĥ çömþŕömîšéð šéçûŕîţý, šûçĥ åš ŕööţéð ðévîçéš. Ŕéšéţ ţĥîš ðévîçé ţö ƒåçţöŕý šéţţîñĝš. ññ• Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð. ñ• Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight]"</string>
    <string name="untrusted_os_policy_compromised_os_incompliant_title">[Ðévîçé šéçûŕîţý ñöţ ţŕûšţéð one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="untrusted_os_policy_compromised_os_incompliant_wipe_warning_do_desc">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ðöéšñ'ţ åļļöŵ ŵöŕķ ðåţå öñ ðévîçéš ŵîţĥ çömþŕömîšéð šéçûŕîţý, šûçĥ åš ŕööţéð ðévîçéš. Ŕéšéţ ţĥîš ðévîçé ţö ƒåçţöŕý šéţţîñĝš. ññ• Ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð. ñ• Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight]"</string>
    <string name="untrusted_os_policy_compromised_os_incompliant_wipe_warning_po_desc">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ðöéšñ'ţ åļļöŵ ŵöŕķ ðåţå öñ ðévîçéš ŵîţĥ çömþŕömîšéð šéçûŕîţý, šûçĥ åš ŕööţéð ðévîçéš. Ŕéšéţ ţĥîš ðévîçé ţö ƒåçţöŕý šéţţîñĝš. ññ• Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ бé ŕémövéð. ñ• Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight]"</string>
    <string name="untrusted_os_policy_incompliant_title">"[Ţĥîš ðévîçé'š ðåţå îš åţ ŕîšķ one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="untrusted_os_policy_unknown_os_incompliant_block_warning_do_desc">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ðöéšñ'ţ åļļöŵ ŵöŕķ ðåţå öñ ðévîçéš ŵîţĥ ûñķñöŵñ öþéŕåţîñĝ šýšţémš. Måķé šûŕé ýöû'ŕé ŕûññîñĝ å ţŕûšţéð véŕšîöñ öƒ Åñðŕöîð, åñð ýöûŕ ðévîçé бööţļöåðéŕ îš ļöçķéð. ññ• Ýöûŕ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð. ñ• Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone]"</string>
    <string name="untrusted_os_policy_unknown_os_incompliant_block_warning_po_desc">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ðöéšñ'ţ åļļöŵ ŵöŕķ ðåţå öñ ðévîçéš ŵîţĥ ûñķñöŵñ öþéŕåţîñĝ šýšţémš. Måķé šûŕé ýöû'ŕé ŕûññîñĝ å ţŕûšţéð véŕšîöñ öƒ Åñðŕöîð, åñð ýöûŕ ðévîçé бööţļöåðéŕ îš ļöçķéð. ññ• Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵîļļ бé бļöçķéð. ñ• Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo]"</string>
    <string name="untrusted_os_policy_unknown_os_incompliant_title">[ÖŠ ñöţ ţŕûšţéð one two]</string>
    <string name="untrusted_os_policy_unknown_os_incompliant_wipe_warning_do_desc">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ðöéšñ'ţ åļļöŵ ŵöŕķ ðåţå öñ ðévîçéš ŵîţĥ ûñķñöŵñ öþéŕåţîñĝ šýšţémš. Måķé šûŕé ýöû'ŕé ŕûññîñĝ å ţŕûšţéð véŕšîöñ öƒ Åñðŕöîð, åñð ýöûŕ ðévîçé бööţļöåðéŕ îš ļöçķéð. ññ• Ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð. ñ• Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone]"</string>
    <string name="untrusted_os_policy_unknown_os_incompliant_wipe_warning_po_desc">"[Ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ðöéšñ'ţ åļļöŵ ŵöŕķ ðåţå öñ ðévîçéš ŵîţĥ ûñķñöŵñ öþéŕåţîñĝ šýšţémš. Måķé šûŕé ýöû'ŕé ŕûññîñĝ å ţŕûšţéð véŕšîöñ öƒ Åñðŕöîð, åñð ýöûŕ ðévîçé бööţļöåðéŕ îš ļöçķéð. ññ• Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ бé ŕémövéð. ñ• Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree twentyfour twentyfive twentysix twentyseven twentyeight twentynine thirty thirtyone thirtytwo]"</string>
    <string name="untrusted_os_policy_wipe_warning_do">[Ţĥîš ðévîçé ŵîļļ бé éŕåšéð. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve]</string>
    <string name="untrusted_os_policy_wipe_warning_po">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé ŵîļļ бé ŕémövéð. Çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ ƒöŕ ĥéļþ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen]</string>
    <string name="url_error">[Ţĥîš ļîñķ çåññöţ бé ðîšþļåýéð. one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="user_action_multi_incompliant_desc">[Ţåþ åñ îţém ţö ŕéšöļvé îţ one two three four five six]</string>
    <string name="user_cancelled_adding_account_message">[Ţö ƒîñîšĥ šéţûþ, šîĝñ îñ ţö ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åççöûñţ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="view_terms">[Vîéŵ ţéŕmš one two]</string>
    <string name="welcome_get_started">[Ĝéţ šţåŕţéð one two]</string>
    <string name="welcome_learn_more">[Ļéåŕñ möŕé one two]</string>
    <string name="welcome_license_info">[Ļîçéñšé îñƒöŕmåţîöñ one two three]</string>
    <string name="wifi_cancel">[Çåñçéļ one]</string>
    <string name="wifi_connect">[Çöññéçţ one]</string>
    <string name="wifi_password">[Þåššŵöŕð one]</string>
    <string name="wifi_saved">[Šåvéð one]</string>
    <string name="wifi_security">[Šéçûŕîţý one]</string>
    <string name="wifi_security_none">[Ñöñé one]</string>
    <string name="wifi_show_password">[Šĥöŵ þåššŵöŕð one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_ssid">[Ñéţŵöŕķ ñåmé one two]</string>
    <string name="wifi_ssid_hint">[Éñţéŕ ţĥé ŠŠÎÐ one two]</string>
    <string name="wipe_reason">Your device was offline for too long</string>
    <string name="work_experience_changing_desc">A work profile will be created that keeps your apps and data separate for work and personal</string>
    <string name="work_experience_changing_title">Your device experience is changing</string>
    <string name="work_profile_cant_be_added_contact_admin">[Å ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé çåñ’ţ бé åððéð ţö ţĥîš ᐅ%1$sᐊ. Îƒ ýöû ĥåvé qûéšţîöñš, çöñţåçţ ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_info">[Ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé îñƒö one two three]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_installing_tutorial_details">[Ýöû çåñ ķééþ ûšîñĝ ýöûŕ ðévîçé ðûŕîñĝ šéţûþ one two three four five six seven eight nine]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_installing_tutorial_title">[Šéţţîñĝ ûþ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļéû2026 one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_provisioning_accept_header_post_suw">"[Ļéţ'š šéţ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five six seven]"</string>
    <string name="work_profile_provisioning_progress_label">[Šéţţîñĝ ûþ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļéû2026 one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_provisioning_step_1_header">[Ŵöŕķ åþþš åŕé ķéþţ îñ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé one two three four five six seven eight]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_provisioning_step_2_header">"[Þåûšé ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵĥéñ ýöû'ŕé ðöñé ƒöŕ ţĥé ðåý one two three four five six seven eight nine]"</string>
    <string name="work_profile_provisioning_step_3_header">[Ðåţå îñ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé îš vîšîбļé ţö ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_provisioning_summary">[Ŵöŕķ åþþš åŕé ķéþţ îñ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé. Ýöû çåñ þåûšé ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ åþþš ŵĥéñ ýöû’ŕé ðöñé ƒöŕ ţĥé ðåý. Ţĥé ðåţå îñ ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé îš vîšîбļé ţö ýöûŕ ÎŢ åðmîñ. one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty twentyone twentytwo twentythree]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_setup_done">[Ýöûŕ ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé îš ŕéåðý ţö ûšé¡ one two three four five six seven]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_setup_failed_content">[Ţåþ ţö ţŕý åĝåîñ one two three four]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_setup_failed_title">"[Ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé îšñ'ţ šéţ ûþ one two three four five six]"</string>
    <string name="work_profile_setup_in_progress_desc">[Ţåþ ţö çöñţîñûé one two]</string>
    <string name="work_profile_setup_in_progress_title">[Ŵöŕķ þŕöƒîļé šéţûþ îñ þŕöĝŕéšš one two three four five six seven]</string>
</resources>
